# DANIEL BATANOV

#### Junior Front-end Developer

**%** 0884044070

batanoff.s@protonmail.com







#### **SUMMARY**

Driven by a fervent passion for coding, I am actively transitioning into a front-end developer role. I have over three years of work experience as an architect and QA tester. A rigorous full-time training regimen at SoftUni has honed my proficiency in React, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS, providing me with a solid technical foundation.

#### **PROJECTS**

### Mini Finance Innovations & github

This responsive platform simulates online banking, offering features such as top-up, friends, transactions, history and more

- Front-end: React, React Router, CSS, HTML
- Backend: Backendless used as backend service
- API: ExchangeRate API for live currency exchange rates
- Design: Ant Design, react-credit-card-2

### ra-auth-ui - open source project

"Ra-auth-ui" is out of the box authentication layouts, hooks and pipelines to integrate into react-admin library

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Architect

**2021 - 2023** 

### IPA architecture and more

- Delivered over 10 architectural projects
- Managed three junior architects while working with other teams
- Being the go-to architect for assignments with short deadlines
- Actively coordinating project requirements and issues with engineers in different departments (HVAC, Electrical, Design etc.)
- Selected to be the BIM architect on the team due to my technical
- · Won monthly award for best BIM architect

### Junior architect

2018 - 2019

Design Art "K&K"

Junior architect

**#** 2017 - 2018

2014 - 2015

Integra Consult Project

### **Quality Assurance**

#### Gameloft

- Developed 100+ unique test cases and processes to remove issues for product launches
- Assisted other teams during overtime to resolve major issues
- Consistently giving feedback to the development team

### ACHIEVEMENTS AND WORKSHOPS

# SoftUniada2024 Programing Olympiad

- · Top 10 in web projects category
- 16th place in the final stage out of an overall 157 participants



### Erasmus + "Youthpass"

Tutor of a social and cultural workshop with Dutch attendance



### Interdisciplinary Student Workshop 2017 Second-best project award

Worked in a team of 8 individuals as a leader to develop an urban project for 7 days

### **EDUCATION**

**Software University** Full-stack developer

🛗 01/2023 - Present

University of Architecture, Civil Engineering and Geodesv

Master of Architecture

### High School of Matematics "Baba Tonka"

**Profile Information Technology** 

### **CERTIFICATES**

**GRADES** 5.81/6.00

in

#### **Basics JavaScript** Variables

Loops

· Conditional Statements

### Fundamentals JavaScript

5.73/6.00

- Data Structures-Map, Set Text Processing
- Functions Classes
- Database Basics Regex

# Advanced JavaScript

### 6.00/6.00

- Statements
- Nested Arrays
- DOM and Events
- Error Handling Prototypes

· Unit Testing

· Advanced Functions Inheritance

### Applications JavaScript

6.00/6.00

6.00/6.00

ongoing

- HTTP REST Services
- · Architecture and Testing · Asynchronous operations · Client Side Rendering
- · Remote Data
- Routing
- SPA and Authentication
  Modular Applications

### HTML & CSS

Flexbox

- · Box Model & Position
- Topography
- · Responsive Design
- Forms

# React Js

JSX syntax

- · Hooks and custom hook
- Components Forms
- Authentication Context

- HigherOrder Components
  Routing

# **SKILLS**

# Tech stack

**JavaScript** React **TypeScript** Bootstrap Git CSS Tailwind SASS

### Soft skills

Communication

Problem-solving

Time management

Motivation

Teamwork

HTML

### Other skills

3dsMax Photoshop Figma

Illustrator

#### LANGUAGES

English Proficient



Bulgarian Native

